Guide to the School of Management, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Management, Yale University, student records
1975-2013
RU 108
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
148.5
(151 boxes)
The records consist of student files maintained by the Yale School of Management (known as the School of Organization and Management prior to 1995).
Yale University. School of Management
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 30-F (YRG 30-F), Student records of the Yale School of Management.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Management, 1991-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The records are restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student files maintained by the Yale School of Management (known as the School of Organization and Management prior to 1995).
Business students; College students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Management; Yale University. School of Organization and Management
- Student records for the Classes of 1978-1986, 1976-1986; Accession 1992-A-002
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Class of 1978
  - Class of 1979
  - Class of 1980
  - Class of 1981
  - Class of 1982
  - Class of 1983
  - Class of 1984
  - Class of 1985
  - Class of 1986
- Student records for the Class of 1987, 1985-1987; Accession 1993-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
- Student records for the Class of 1988, 1986-1988; Accession 1994-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1989, 1987-1989; Accession 1994-A-118
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1990, 1988-1990; Accession 1995-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - WITHDREW, 1988-1990
- Student records for the Class of 1991, 1989-1991; Accession 1996-A-062
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1992, 1990-1992; Accession 1998-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
- Student records for the Class of 1993, 1991-1993; Accession 1998-A-106
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - WITHDREW, 1991-1993
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1992-1994; Accession 1999-A-090
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - WITHDREW
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1993-1995; Accession 2001-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - WITHDREW
  - DECEASED
- Student records for the Class of 1996, 1994-1996; Accession 2001-A-134
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1995-1997; Accession 2003-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 1998, 1996-1998; Accession 2004-A-071
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - WITHDREW
  - DECEASED
- Student admission records, 1993-2002; Accession 2004-A-078
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Class of 1993
  - Class of 1994
  - Class of 1995
  - Class of 1996
  - Class of 1997
  - Class of 1998
  - Class of 1999
  - Class of 2000
  - Class of 2001
  - Class of 2002
- Student records for the Class of 1999, 1997-1999; Accession 2005-A-135
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
- Student records for the Classes of 2000-2001, 1998-2001; Accession 2007-A-149
  - Class of 2000
    - Withdrew:
  - Class of 2001
    - Withdrawns:
- Student records for the Classes of 2003-2005, 2001-2005; Accession 2007-A-062
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
  - Class of 2003
  - Class of 2004
  - Class of 2005
- Student records for the Class of 2006, 2004-2006; Accession 2008-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2082
  - Enrollment forms, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 216 - 217)
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 2000-2002; Accession 2008-A-100
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Withdrawns
- Student records for the Class of 2003, 2001-2003; Accession 2009-A-028
  These records are restricted until 2079.
  - WITHDRAWN:
- Student admission records for the Class of 2007, 2005; Accession 2009-A-032
  Restricted until January 1, 2083.
- Student admission records for the Class of 2008, 2006; Accession 2010-A-014
- Student records for the Classes of 2004-2005, 2002-2005; Accession 2011-A-018
  - Class of 2004
    - WITHDRAWN
  - Class of 2005
    - Withdrawals, 2003-2005
- Student records for the Classes of 2006-2007, 2005-2012; Accession 2012-A-093
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2087
  - Class of 2006
    - New Orleans Universities (1 or 2 semesters only)
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 2007
    - Withdrew/Expelled
- Student records for the Classes of 2008 and 2009, 2008-2009; Accession 2013-A-075
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
  - Class of 2008
    - Expelled
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 2009
    - Exchange program
    - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Classes of 2010-2013, 2007-2013; Accession 2014-A-018
  Restricted until January 1, 2088
  - Class of 2010
    - Exchange Students
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 2011
    - Exchange Students
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 2012
    - Exchange Students
    - Expelled
  - Class of 2013
    - Exchange Students